var questions = [{
	"question": "Which of the following function is used to get environment variables in PHP?",
	"option1": "search()",
	"option2": "environment()",
	"option3": "eve()",
	"option4": "getenv()",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "Which of the following function is used to read the content of a file?",
	"option1": "fopen() ",
	"option2": "fread()",
	"option3": "filesize() ",
	"option4": "file_exit()",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": " Which of the following provides the error code associated with this file upload?",
	"option1": "$_FILE['file']['error']",
	"option2": "$_FILE['file']['name'] ",
	"option3": "$_FILE['file']['size']",
	"option4": "$_FILE['file']['type']",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Code that uses a class, function, or method is often described as the..",
	"option1": "client code",
	"option2": "user code",
	"option3": "object code",
	"option4": "class code",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": " Which keyword precedes a method name?",
	"option1": "method",
	"option2": "function",
	"option3": "public",
	"option4": "protected",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Which one of the following is the right description for the method getMessage() ?",
	"option1": "Returns the message if it is passed to the constructor",
	"option2": "Returns the message if it is passed to the class",
	"option3": "Returns the message if it is passed to the file",
	"option4": "Returns the message if it is passed to the object",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "  Which one of the following regular expression matches any string containing zero or one p",
	"option1": "p+",
	"option2": "p*",
	"option3": "p?",
	"option4": "p#",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "How many functions does PHP offer for searching strings using POSIX style regular expression?",
	"option1": "7",
	"option2": "8",
	"option3": "9",
	"option4": "10",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": " Which function is used to split a string into a series of substrings, with each string boundary is determined by a specific separator?",
	"option1": "break()",
	"option2": "divide()",
	"option3": "explode()",
	"option4": "md5()",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": " Which is the most powerful authentication method among the four?",
	"option1": "Hard-coding a login pair directly into the script",
	"option2": "File-based authentication",
	"option3": " Data-based authentication",
	"option4": "PEARâ€™S HTTP authentication",
	"answer": "3"
}];